eleafworld.com 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy

                                  Privacy Policy
About us
This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you, how we may use it
and the steps we take to ensure that it is kept secure. We also explain your rights and how
to contact us.
BY USING THIS WEBSITE AND GIVING YOUR INFORMATION TO US, YOU INDICATE
YOUR CONSENT TO US COLLECTING AND USING YOUR PERSONAL
INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS SET OUT IN THIS POLICY.
What Information We Collect About You
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. When
registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail
address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
How We Will Use Your Information
All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used, and protected by
us in accordance with current data protection legislation, our Terms and Conditions and
this Privacy Policy. We may use your personal information:
* To identify visitors to this website;
* To promote our products and/or services;
* To provide the products and/or services you request from us;
* To communicate with you in the event that any services you have requested are
currently unavailable;
* To carry out market research and analysis your feedback so that we can improve the
services we offer;
* To send periodic emails with occasional company news, updates, related product or
service information, etc.
You can tell us not to contact you at any point by e-mailing us at service@eleafworld.com
How We Disclose Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable

information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our
website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep
this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe
release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or
others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information
may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How to Control Your Personal Information
If allowed by applicable laws, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time
when we processes your personal information based on your consent. However,
withdrawal does not affect the legitimacy and effectiveness of how we process your
personal information based on your consent before the withdrawal is made; nor does it
affect any information processing based on another justification other than your consent.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
The security of your personal information is important to us. We use appropriate physical,
management, and technical measures to protect your personal information from
unauthorized access, disclosure, use, modification, damage, or loss.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not
to information collected offline.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy
statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware
of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we
disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it
frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or
by means of a notice on our home page.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions, please contact service@eleafworld.com.
